[music]
>> Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the
stage BRAD WILLIAMS.
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> LEXINGTON, KENTUCKY. HOW THE HELL WE
FEELING OUT THERE TONIGHT?
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> HELL YEAH. THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH for
being here. Holy crap, are we going to
have a lot of fun. From the moment I got
here in Lexington and told people I was
shooting my special, everyone just
looked at me and went, "Why?"
And I was like, "Don't you know? This
theater is literally on Short Street."
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> HOW COULD I NOT shoot my special in
Lexington, Kentucky?
And thank you guys for being here.
Tomorrow, when when when someone says,
"Hey, you were in Kentucky last night.
What you doing Kentucky last night?" You
get to respond, "Bourbon and midgets."
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Bourbon and midgets, that's a damn good
night of comedy.
That's a really weird night on Pornhub.
I'm not going to lie. I've been married
8 years. I'm watching way too much adult
content. I am. I am. I'm watching too
much. I'M TRYING TO STOP, BUT THEY KEEP
COMING out with new episodes.
I got to find out what happens to that
plumber.
Dude, I don't know like I just think
there's too much. I think we have too
much adult content on the internet. I
really do. I think we have too much cuz
we have everything. We have everything.
We should not have everything.
I'm all for freedom of expression, but
at some point when you're typing in what
you want, IT SHOULD WRITE BACK, "NO."
"YOU have a family." Like it should.
But it never does. You can type in
anything you want. You type in chocolate
syrup titties, it'll be like Hershey or
Nestle. Crazy.
There's too much. There's too much adult
content on the internet. I know cuz I
got to the end of it.
They sent me a t-shirt. It was very
nice.
They should have sent me a sock.
Oh, if that joke offended you, it's
going to be a long [\h__\h] night for
you. All right.
>> [applause]
>> Now, we all know there's weird stuff out
there. We know there's weird stuff on
the internet. I just don't know if you
know how weird it gets, okay? Like I
said, I've been there. I know how weird
it gets. Did you know there's an entire
category of adult entertainment that's
just naked women sitting on balloons?
And
This front row's like, "Yeah, he used to
describe my Tuesday." OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU KNOW WHAT NOW YOU KNOW I'M NOT
LYING. I DIDN'T MAKE IT UP. This little
like this little section right here is
like, "Hell yeah." Like that Okay.
EVERYONE ELSE WAS LIKE, "NAKED women
sitting on balloons, what comes AFTER
THAT?"
THEM.
>> [applause]
>> THEY COME right after that. They see a
naked woman pop a balloon, they're like,
"That's what daddy needed. PILE IT ON."
AND DON'T GET ME WRONG, I'M NOT TRYING
to kink shame. If you're out there and
you're into some weird stuff, that's
okay. It's okay to be into weird stuff.
As long as it doesn't hurt anybody, as
long as everyone involved is a
consenting adult, great. Let your freak
flag fly. Go [\h__\h] nuts. If balloon
porn is your thing, okay. Balloon porn
is your thing. Here's my only question.
How the [\h__\h] do you find out balloon
porn is your thing? How do you find that
out?
CUZ YOU FOUND OUT ONE DAY. ONE DAY
DIDN'T KNOW IT EXISTED. Next day,
MASTURBATING. WHAT THE [\h__\h] HAPPENED IN
THAT 24 HOURS? What went down? Did you
go to children's party? You see A MOM
TRIP, FALL on balloon, it pops, you're
like, "Oh my god." And what happened?
Do your friends know?
Are they saying things like, "WE'RE
GOING TO CHUCK-E-CHEESE. Can't bring
you." Is that a thing?
There's a lot of weird stuff out there.
There's a lot of weird stuff that people
are into. There's dudes out there that
are into feet.
Feet.
Once again, not judging. If you're into
feet, okay, not that bad. I just don't
know why. I don't know how. How? How
does someone look at a woman with face,
tits, ass, and be like, "But where's
that foot though?" Okay, I don't get it.
Maybe I've never seen the right foot.
Cuz I've never seen that [\h__\h] foot,
all right? I've never seen a foot that
made me go, "Move them titties." Okay, I
I I've never seen that foot.
I think feet are [\h__\h] disgusting. I
see any foot, I'm just I can't I can't
with feet. I can't.
But here's how you know you can't choose
what you're into. You can't choose your
kink. You can't choose your fetish. Cuz
if I could choose what I was into,
I would absolutely choose feet. I wish I
was into feet. Do you have any idea how
amazing
my life would be
if I was into feet?
With how low I am to the ground,
oh my god, I would never go to work. I
would just run around looking for
sandals. Just [\h__\h] yeah. [\h__\h] yeah. [\h__\h]
yeah. [\h__\h] yeah. [\h__\h] yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
>> [applause]
>> I would just run down a beach and just
tickle [\h__\h]
And be honest with yourselves for 1
second. If you were ever just lying on a
beach getting a tan, just relaxing, and
a dwarf
just ran up
and started tickling your toes,
none of you would be mad. Not one person
in here would be mad.
Not one. A dwarf runs up, tickles your
toes, you'd all BE LIKE, "AH,
I'M GETTING THREE WISHES."
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> PEOPLE ARE OUT THERE. A lot of people
are into weird stuff. I feel very lucky
that I'm a basic [\h__\h]
Very simple things get me excited. I
don't need a lot of pomp and
circumstance. Very simple things. I've
been married 8 years, and every time my
wife gets naked, I'M STILL, "YAY!
I'M HAPPY.
I'M VERY THANKFUL, YOU KNOW? I'M GLAD
I'm not into weird [\h__\h] I'm glad every
time we want to have sex, I don't have
to be like, "Hold on, I got to go charge
a car battery."
All right, I'm glad.
Yes, I'm married. Uh I've been married
for 8 years. My wife is A TALL WOMAN.
>> [laughter]
>> I KNOW. I DID IT.
NOW, WHY DO I TELL YOU THAT? I tell you
that because when I tell people I'm
married, a lot of people just assume,
"Oh, he found another one."
>> [snorts]
[laughter]
>> Not the case. That is not what happened.
My wife is not a dwarf. I did not meet
her in a wood.
I wasn't just out there knocking on tree
stumps like, "Daddy's got to get laid."
Okay? Like like that did not happen.
Now, that does not mean I don't find
dwarf women attractive. I do. I've dated
several in my past. I just didn't want
to marry a dwarf woman. I didn't want to
marry a dwarf. I don't want to marry
another little person. I don't want to
be sitting there in our home, me and my
dwarf wife, and all of a sudden a light
bulb burns out and I got to be like,
>> [laughter]
>> "We're fucked."
That room just has to be dark now.
Cuz that could happen TO ME. THAT'S
SOMETHING YOU GUYS DON'T THINK ABOUT.
HERE'S A STORY FOR YOU. BACK WHEN I WAS
SINGLE, I had an apartment, and a buddy
of mine came over, stayed overnight, and
before he left the next morning to go to
work, he took a shower. And when he left
THE SHOWER, HE ADJUSTED MY SHOWER HEAD.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT THE [\h__\h] THAT DID
TO MY DAY? DO YOU UNDERSTAND? DO YOU
WHAT I HAD TO CALL A HANDYMAN? A
HANDYMAN A HANDYMAN HAD TO COME OVER TO
MY HOUSE. HE BROUGHT a tool belt. He
didn't need one. All right.
I had to give him money. I had to GIVE
HIM LEGAL TENDER FOR THIS GUY TO JUST GO
INTO MY BATHROOM AND GO
EAT. JUST LIKE THAT.
>> [applause]
>> That eat cost me $65.
Yes, my wife is a tall woman and I just
didn't want to marry another dwarf. I
didn't I I didn't want to have a dwarf
wife. I don't want to hug my wife and we
look like the top of a wedding cake. All
right.
No, my wife is a tall woman. I hug her,
we look like the cake you buy a woman
who just got custody of a 7-year-old.
Wife is a tall woman. She's also Asian.
Yes.
Oh, your boy is doing well. Now.
Why do I tell you that? Why do I tell
you that my wife is a tall, beautiful
Asian woman? Am I bragging?
Yes.
I'm bragging, but also, and this is
real, I'm just trying to give some
lonely men out there
a little bit of hope.
I'm trying to let you know it can happen
for you. I know there's dudes out there.
I know some of you are lonely, some of
you get angry. I'm trying to let you
know if you're over the age of 25 and
you're a dude and you can't get laid,
you can't get a date, and the women
aren't talking to you, I'm here to tell
you
it's [\h__\h] you.
It's you. Congratulations.
We found the problem, all right?
>> [applause]
>> It's you. [cheering]
Stop blaming your issues on the [\h__\h]
OKAY? IT'S NOT THEM. But guess what? NOW
WE KNOW IT'S YOU. Now we know what the
problem is and now we can change it and
we need to change it cuz right now in
the game of life you're losing and
you're losing to [\h__\h] this, okay?
>> [applause]
>> But now you know the problem, you can do
what you got to do to improve that. You
can go get some therapy, go to the gym,
become a better person cuz that's what I
had to do. I had to become a decent
person to meet someone like my wife. My
wife didn't have to do [\h__\h]
Cuz you see my wife, you could tell. You
could tell why she is, was, and will
always be my dream woman.
Yeah. Come on. Come [cheering] on.
>> [applause]
>> This was not her dream.
No, this was not her dream. My wife
wasn't a little girl just having
daydreams of your FUTURE GOING, "ONE
DAY!
ONE DAY I'M GOING TO buy my husband's
clothes at a Build-A-Bear."
My wife didn't watch Snow White like,
"I'm going to [\h__\h] one of those."
I had to become a decent human being to
be with a woman like my wife. Now, I
wasn't always a decent human being. I
was in my 20s, I was single, I've done
some [\h__\h] okay? Of course I've done
some [\h__\h] People like, "Brad, you were
kinky in your 20s?" Of course I was
kinky in my 20s. Look at me,
If you look like this, you've done some
kinky [\h__\h] No average-sized woman ever
[\h__\h] a dwarf with great self-esteem.
That does not happen.
No, I've done some [\h__\h] A woman painted
me blue one time.
Yes. Yes. Not a metaphor. We weren't on
our way to a University of Kentucky
basketball game. No, okay?
>> [cheering]
>> No.
Cuz that would make sense. No. This was
out of nowhere just like, "Ooh, I'm
going to paint you blue." And I was
like, "No, you're not. That's kind of
creepy. That's not going to happen."
She's like, "You're going to be my
Smurf." I'm like, "It got weirder. Oh my
god. Uh
No, not into that. I'll do a lot, but
even that makes me a little
uncomfortable, so that's not happening.
But then she showed me them titties and
I was like la la la la la la la la la
hey.
>> [applause]
>> Oh yeah.
All the night started off real weird. By
the end of the night she was calling me
Papa Smurf.
Yes.
I've done some [\h__\h] in my life. Cuz you
got to understand when I'm out there
when when I was single, it's different
than when you guys are out there. When
you guys are out there and you're
single, you find someone, you hook up,
you [\h__\h] When you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] for
you. When I [\h__\h] I'm [\h__\h] on behalf
of a people.
All right.
That's a lot of pressure. I would feel
that pressure every time every time I
was with a tall woman I would picture
every dwarf in the world at the foot of
my bed just cheering me on the entire
time.
The bed's high. They can't see what's
happening up there. It's a double
decker.
>> [applause]
>> I had a wild time in my 20s. I said yes.
I got a lot of stories. I had range in
my 20s. Oh yeah, the smallest girl I
ever dated was 3'7. And the tallest
woman I ever dated was 6'2.
And now we know which sex tape you would
prefer to watch.
Roll the clip.
Yes, I dated a 6'2 woman at one point in
my life. It was a fun relationship. At
one point obviously it had to end. And I
felt bad when it ended cuz I ended it. I
broke up with her. And I felt bad
anytime I broke up with a tall woman cuz
you get dumped by a dwarf?
That's not a highlight of the resume,
you know.
And I'm not saying that cuz I'm a catch
or anything. I'm just saying it's a
little awkward when 4'4 walks up to you
and goes, "I think it's you." Okay, it's
weird.
What was even weirder was the reason why
I had to break up with her. Now I'll
tell you the reason, but before I do,
please understand I know now that this
is not her fault and not her issue. This
was my fault and my issue, okay? So, now
that you know that, I'll tell you why I
broke up with her. I had to break up
with her because every time we had sex
the queefs.
It was a lot, okay? The queef You guys
You guys know what queefs are, right?
You guys know the little [\h__\h] You know
the little [\h__\h] farts, do you guys know
what that is? Yeah. And normally that's
all they are, just just like that. And
you can power through that. This was not
like that. No, this was like letting the
air out of a balloon, just
like that.
The whole time. AND SHE'S 6'2". SHE'S
6'2".
EVERY TIME SHE QUEEFED, I THOUGHT SHE
WAS GOING TO BLOW ME INTO A ceiling fan.
How did Brad die? Hilariously.
>> [applause]
>> He was killed by his biggest fan.
AND ONCE AGAIN, NOT HER FAULT, NOT HER
FAULT. I DO NOT BLAME HER. If you know
the science behind that, you know that
it was my fault. You know the queef only
happened because I don't possess
the necessary equipment
to make an AIRTIGHT SEAL, OKAY? YOU KNOW
THAT.
NO, I CAN'T DO THAT. I CAN'T MAKE an
airtight seal. I was in there, it was a
screen door in a hurricane, okay? It was
tall.
>> [applause]
>> Only way I can make a seal is if I had a
circus cannon and a head start, just
>> [applause]
>> I've done some [\h__\h]
But I'm happy I did.
I'm glad I did all that wild stuff in my
20s. You should do wild stuff in your
20s. So, when you get get the point
where you're ready to settle down, you
don't regret not doing the wild stuff.
So, I'm glad I did the wild stuff. And I
did plenty. One time, I had sex with a
310-lb woman.
Now you [\h__\h] get quiet, okay?
No, it was great. It was awesome. She
was so sweet. She was so much fun. She
made me laugh, made me feel good about
myself, and she wanted to have sex with
me. In my opinion, if you want to have
sex with me, you're a good person.
And I don't want to make sure she was
comfortable. So, I looked at her and
went, "Hey, I get what's about to
happen. I'm just letting you know,
tonight not about me. Don't worry about
me. Tonight's about you. Tonight's about
you. What can I do for you? How can I
make you happy? How can I make you come?
What's your favorite position?" She's
like, "I love it on top." I was like,
"Oh, god."
What's your second favorite position?
She said, "You get on top." I WAS LIKE,
"HELL YEAH." SO,
so I hopped on.
I had to, but then
once I got on top, I ran into a whole
new set of problems. Now, I'm not saying
this to be gross or to exploit this
woman. I'm saying this cuz this is what
happened. This is the story. This is how
it went down. I got on top, and that's
when I realized this woman was so big
and my arms
are so small.
I couldn't touch the ground when I was
on top of this woman.
Do you understand what I'm trying to say
here, okay? I'm not going to get too
graphic, but you get it, right? Like I
couldn't I I couldn't I couldn't touch
the ground.
I got no traction, okay? Like I I I got
no traction.
None. None. At that point, I wasn't even
[\h__\h] I was floating.
You know what I look like? I look like
one of those ducks you buy at Walmart,
you stick them on the front yard, the
wings just spin in the wind, like that.
That's what it looked like.
Like two guys will be over here having a
conversation. How's the weather today,
Bob? Well, according to the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] the fat chick over there, it's
strong winds out of the southeast.
But this is why this is why this woman
will always have a place near and dear
to my heart and why I do not want you to
think I am not thankful for every
interaction I had with her cuz that was
a very awkward moment. Very awkward
moment. She could have let it be an
awkward moment. She could have let it
ruin the night. No one would have blamed
her, but she didn't. She was determined
to have a good time. I got on top. I
couldn't touch the ground. She saw and
she's like, "Don't worry, baby. I got
you."
>> [laughter]
[applause]
[cheering]
>> Bro.
I don't know if any of y'all have ever
role-played as a stick shift before.
That night daddy got dropped into
fourth, okay?
And she was into it, too. At one point
she EVEN YELLED OUT, "FASTER!" AND I'M
LIKE, "I'M NOT IN CONTROL OF THE
SITUATION."
NOW, why do I tell you that? Why do I
tell you these stories?
I tell you these stories cuz I'm trying
to let you know it's okay to be a little
bit freaky.
It's okay to have a little fun. Find a
partner who is into the same freaky
stuff that you're into. And if your
partner, who you love and you trust,
comes to you and goes, "Hey, there's
this thing. I've always wanted to try
it. I'm a little uncomfortable, but I
feel safe with you. So, can we try it
together?
>> [gasps]
>> Give it a go. Have some fun.
Now, I know I say that every dude just
looked at his woman like, "See, anal."
Just say, "Wow."
You don't have to do that, okay? You
don't have to do anything you don't want
to do. Have precautions in place. Have a
safe word. Safe words are fine. They're
normal. You're allowed a safe word
during sex, you know, you got to stop,
reevaluate your situation, make sure
everyone is comfortable with how you're
proceeding. Safe words are healthy. A
lot of healthy, normal couples have
them. You know, I'm sure there's couples
here tonight that have a safe word. I I
don't know if anyone wants to share what
their safe
Wait, what what Sorry, what was that?
>> Galliwasper.
>> [laughter]
>> Did you say galliwasper?
>> Galliwasper.
>> Is that a last name of a Kentucky
player? What the [\h__\h] is that?
Doesn't that sound like one? Like, "OH,
WHAT A MOVE by galliwasper." Like that.
Either that or that sounds like really
old southern slang, like that's a racial
slur. It kind of does, right? Like,
"Look at William [\h__\h] galliwaspers
over there."
Is galliwasper an actual thing?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
What is it?
What's a galliwasper?
>> Like you're explaining a big fish. You
caught a galliwasper.
>> Oh, galliwasper. Oh, it's a big fish.
You shouldn't talk about your wife's
area in fish terms.
>> [applause]
[laughter]
>> So So, you're just doing some [\h__\h] like
she's choking you or she puts a finger
in your ass and you just yell out and
you just stare at her [\h__\h] and go,
"Galliwasper." And then she looks at you
and go, "Well, if I wasn't working with
a minnow."
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Let's try to do one more. Let's try to
do one more. Who's got Who's got one?
>> Muskrat.
>> Muskrat?
No.
If If you look at your man's dick and
yell out the name of a rodent, oh my
god.
You know what though? That would That
would do the trick. That would I would I
would stop [\h__\h] you if you looked
If you looked at my dick and was like,
"Field mouse." I'd be like, "Hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey hey HEY HEY HEY HEY
HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY
HEY HEY HEY HEY HEY
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S A MONGOOSE. OKAY, I WOULD
[applause]
>> BUT SEE, HERE'S THE THING. HERE'S THE
THING. I ACTUALLY like that word. I like
galliwasper as a safe word, okay? It's a
little long, hard to say with a ball gag
in your mouth, but
I like it. I like it as a safe word
because it stands out. Your safe word
has to stand out. It can't be something
you say all the time, is always in your
common vernacular, you know? Like my
safe word can't be, "Can you reach
that?"
Now,
my wife and I, we have a safe word, but
our safe word has nothing to do with sex
at all. Our safe word's for something
completely different, but still vital to
the success of our marriage. Feel free
to adopt this if you feel it'll help
you. This is real. My wife and I have a
safe word for when I take a joke too
far.
Yeah, very real.
Cuz I'm a comedian, and I'm always in
comedian brain. You just saw what
happened. Someone suggests some [\h__\h]
and I go, "Ooh, what's funny about that?
What's funny about that? What's funny
about that?" And I say it. I don't think
about the consequences of the joke. I
just think, "Is the joke funny?" If I
think about the consequences, I might
hesitate and then the joke will lose its
power, lose its lose its confidence. So,
I have to just deliver it like I know
this is the funniest joke in the world,
no matter what the evil, dirty, [\h__\h]
up, psychotic thought is. That makes me
a pretty good comedian, it makes me a
horrible person. All right?
So, sometimes I go too far, my wife gets
uncomfortable, and then she will say the
word cephalopod. If I
You didn't [\h__\h] laugh at galley
water. BRO, WHEN THAT GUY SAID THAT
[\h__\h]
YES, CEPHALOPOD. It's my wife's favorite
mollusk. You don't like it? I don't
know.
Weird that our the things are both
seafood.
>> [laughter]
>> It's really awkward when we get boners
at Red Lobster.
Um
But yes, when I hear cephalopod, I know
she's uncomfortable and that's when I
got to back off and I need this in my
life. When our daughter was born, 5
years ago, it was a crazy scenario in
the hospital. Everyone who's been there
knows it's chaos in there. There's
doctors, there's nurses running around.
My wife is on the delivery room table,
just being a champ. Our daughter enters
the world for the very first time, and I
just YELLED OUT, "THE PROPHECY HAS been
fulfilled!"
>> [applause]
>> My wife, as drugged up as she was, was
like, "Cephalopod." And I was like,
"Yeah, you're right."
Fair.
Cuz guys, it doesn't matter if the joke
is there, I have to say the joke. It
doesn't matter who the audience is. It
could be an audience of over a thousand
like tonight. It could be an audience of
one. I do not see a difference. If I
think the joke is funny, I have to say
the joke.
My wife and I were having a very serious
one-on-one conversation right after our
daughter was born. We had to have this
conversation cuz as I mentioned earlier,
we come from different cultural
backgrounds. We had to discuss how we're
going to raise our child. What were we
going to do? We come from different
places, mixed-race relationship. My
wife's Chinese. I'm
not.
No, I'm not Chinese. My Great Wall is a
curb.
Picture it. You're going to laugh again.
So, we're having this discussion. She's
like, "How are we going to raise this
kid? Are we going to raise her more
Chinese or more white?" And I look at
her and go, "Well,
she's female and still alive, SO I GUESS
WHITE."
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> If you laughed at that joke, you're a
horrible human being.
>> [applause]
>> Good people are just staring at ME LIKE,
"STEPH LEPPAD, [screaming] YES!"
I KNOW. COMEDIAN BRAIN, ALWAYS ON. CAN'T
FLIP THE SWITCH. Can't do it. Wish I
could. Wish I could just flip a switch
and it's like, "Okay, now I'm in dad
mode, husband mode, normal [\h__\h] mode."
Can't do it. Even when I'm in situations
where I know I have to be a clear and
present good father and partner. I can't
do it. Prime example, um, couple months
ago, big moment in our family. It was,
it was our daughter's first day of
school. First day of school at the big
school. Aw, that's a big day. That's a
proud day for parents. And it was proud
for us. We were so happy. So, we brought
her to school. Me and my wife brought
her to school. I'm taking photos to send
to the family. My wife is explaining to
her how her day's going to go, so she's
not going to be surprised or stressed
out. And my daughter, little angel, is
just smiling, happy, looking at my wife
just walking to school, but she's
looking at my wife. She's not looking
straight ahead. And in the entrance way
of the school, there's a support pole
that holds up the hallway, right in the
middle of it. My daughter doesn't see it
and just
nails it, okay? Nails it, falls right
over. Now, my daughter is also a dwarf.
She's a little person just like me. And
that's the day I found out that when a a
falls over, no one knows what the [\h__\h]
to do.
Everyone's confused. THESE ARE TRADE
PROFESSIONALS. ALL LIKE, "THIS was not
covered in a meeting."
"What happens now? A dwarf just fell
over. What happens next? Does she
explode into gold coins? I don't know."
No one knows what to do. It's awkwardly
silent. I don't do well with awkward
silences. So, I just BLURTED OUT, "WELL,
I FAIL as a father. I didn't keep my
daughter off the pole."
And now I'm not allowed at school
drop-off anymore.
>> [applause]
>> I wish I could just have a normal night.
I wish I could just have a normal night,
come home like a normal father, see my
family, we sit down have a family meal
together, you know, then we put the kid
to bed, wife and I curl up on the couch,
watch a little TV, have a glass of
Kentucky bourbon, [\h__\h] go to sleep. I
wish that could be my night, cuz that
sounds like the perfect night, doesn't
it?
It can't but it can't be my night, cuz
if I see some stupid [\h__\h] come on the
TV, I have to comment on the stupid [\h__\h]
on the TV, all right? And these are
shows my wife likes, so when I insult
them, she doesn't take it as I'm
insulting the show, she takes it as I'm
insulting her. I have cock-blocked
MYSELF SO MANY TIMES
TO THE POINT NOW where my wife is
watching boring TV shows on purpose so I
have no material to work with. Yes, she
loves cooking competition shows. She
loves them. All the chops, all the Beat
Bobby Flays, she loves them. Her
favorite show right now is this show
called Guy's Grocery Games, okay? Now,
yes, couple of you know the show. All
right, now, if you like it, great. I
don't like it, but I like spending time
with my wife, so I'll watch it with her.
And if you've seen this show, you know
this show, you know the episode I am
about to describe is real. I am not
making this up. Feel free to look for it
and watch it after this, okay? The
episode starts off, Guy Fieri comes out
and goes, "Tonight, on a very unique
episode of Guy's Grocery Games, every
chef in the kitchen tonight has a
developmental disability. Tonight, we
are raising money for charities that
help those with developmental
disabilities. These are wonderful
charities, they do amazing work, they
offer a sense of purpose, a sense of
freedom, a sense of pride.
We we we have nothing but confidence and
we are thankful to support such amazing
charities. And every chef in our kitchen
tonight will be paired with a master
chef to help guide them along the way."
This comes on our television, and my
wife just looks at me and goes, "I
[\h__\h] dare you."
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> You know, they're all going to use the
slow cooker.
>> [applause]
>> You guys ever had Guy Fieri on your sofa
platter you threw a television cuz I
have?
Can't stop. Can't. I don't know if other
husbands have to go through this [\h__\h] I
don't know if other husbands in the room
when you're about to have company come
over, do your wives sit you down and
give you your behavioral expectations
for the evening?
Every time, my wife looks at me, "Okay,
we're having people over tonight. These
are nice people. These are good people.
They're not your [\h__\h] friends, okay?
So,
tonight, for one night, could you just
cool it with the damn jokes?" And I'm
sitting there like, "Oh, the damn jokes
paid for the [\h__\h] house, but okay,
yeah."
We had one of these nights not too long
ago.
Uh, we threw a party and we just moved
into this new neighborhood and we got
this new house and my wife remodeled the
kitchen and now it's like her dream
kitchen and she loves it. So, we we we
we threw a party to introduce ourselves
to all the neighbors. We invited
everybody. Friends, family, neighbors,
gay couple down the street, everybody
comes over. And my wife is just showing
off this kitchen. She is in her element.
Just look at this kitchen. Look at the
island. Look at the refrigerator. Check
out these cabinets. Look at that
backsplash. And one of the gay guys is
like, "I love a backsplash." And I said,
"I bet you do."
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> You're right, cephalopod. I'm going to
bed. All right.
And don't get me wrong. I'm trying to
get better. I'm trying to get better. I
know I need to get better. I know that
once you get married, your job is not
done improving. You got to always be
looking to improve, become a better
person, be the person that your partner
wants to be with. You got to do that cuz
I have to do that cuz it's hard to be
with me. It's not easy. I'm gone a lot.
Last year, out of 52 weeks, I was gone
44 out of those 52. Yeah, that's a lot.
So, when the year was over, I sat my
wife down. I was like, "Hey, I know I
was gone a lot and we're having success
professionally, but I know this year was
hard on you. I just want to tell you how
much you killed it. You you a damn rock
star this year. You were the engine that
makes our family go. It cannot run
without you. And if you don't believe
it, look at our daughter. Look at how
amazing she is. That's a reflection of
how good you are. She is a reflection of
you, and this is why I love you so much.
And let me reward you. Let me get you
something. Let me get you a big gift to
tell you how much I appreciate how hard
you worked. And my wife, very humble
woman, just oh, I don't know.
I've always wanted a king-size bed. And
I'm like, hell yeah, I'll get you a
king-size bed. I said that out loud. And
then I thought,
why the [\h__\h] does she need a king-size
bed? Like,
she doesn't need a king-size bed. SHE
MARRIED ME. SHE DOES NOT NEED A
KING-SIZE BED. WE HAVE A FOAL AND two
pitbulls, and my wife could STILL GO,
YEAH!
>> [screaming]
>> NO! YOU NEED MORE SPACE, FINE. I'LL
SLEEP ON THE OTTOMAN. IT'S OKAY.
I'M NOT hard to please. Pull out a
drawer, put in a pillow, Brad's got a
bed, okay? It's not
But the wife wants a king-size bed, so
damn it, I'm going to get her one. So, I
I I'd say, all right, what kind of bed
are we going to get? And I don't know if
you guys have shopped for beds recently.
Holy crap, have they changed? Uh, it
used to be they were just beds,
mattresses, box springs, that's it. Now,
there's options. There's There There's
batteries. There's tech support ON A
[\h__\h] BED. THERE'S SIDES THAT GO UP
AND DOWN like that. There's Bluetooth
speakers, mood lighting. My wife tells
me, hey, get the one with the climate
zones. And I'm like, the [\h__\h] is a
climate zone besides expensive, okay?
What is it? And my wife goes, oh, it's
great. It gets hotter or colder based on
what you find the most comfortable. AND
I SAID, OH, like a blanket?
That was not the right thing to say.
But she wants the bed. God knows she's
earned it. So, I'm going to go find that
bed. And I go and I find the bed, okay?
It's got everything, all the bells, all
the whistles. I bring it home. I show my
wife. She gasps. She's happy. We bring
it upstairs. We take We put it together.
Then my wife gets on the bed and she
smiles. And let me tell you guys, I live
for that. I live for that smile. And
then she looks at me and then she gives
me a come hither look.
I also live for come hither looks, okay?
I do. She looks at me like, "Get over
here." I've been married 8 years, okay?
I don't get the come hither look as much
as I used to. So now when my wife looks
at me and she says, "Come."
I hither, okay?
So I'm hithering, right? I'm hithering.
And that's when I FOUND OUT I CAN'T GET
ON THIS [\h__\h] BED.
IT'S A KING-SIZE BED. NOW I'M THE DWARF
I TALKED ABOUT EARLIER TRYING TO WATCH
ME [\h__\h] OKAY? THAT'S WHO I AM.
I CAN'T GET ON THE BED. I'M TRYING TO.
I'M TRYING TO PULL MYSELF UP DOING LIKE
SOME dwarf CrossFit [\h__\h] I'm trying to
like pull myself up. That's not working.
My wife is like, "JUST JUMP UP HERE."
I'm like, "JUMP? WHO THE [\h__\h] DO YOU
THINK YOU MARRIED? JUMP? WHAT THE HELL?
NO, I'm not jumping. My people don't
jump. We have a lot of stereotypes,
sure. We live in trees. We make cookies.
We all know those. But you want to know
what stereotypes we don't have? Hops.
Don't have that. Don't have that. No
one's ever done this. "Hey, look a
dwarf." Okay, that's never happened.
And my wife is like, "Well, I can just
toss you up on the bed." And I'm like,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa, the [\h__\h] whoa, okay?
We're not tossing. No one's tossing. My
people do not like to be tossed. I do
not like to be tossed. There was one
time in Afghanistan a long time ago. But
Exactly. If you saw one of the previous
specials, you know. There's one time.
One time.
But no, we're not tossing me. I do not
like to be tossed. If you ever see me
get tossed onto my bed, you know that's
when I'm making some serious [\h__\h]
money, okay?
Right? If you walk into my house there's
just a dude in a suit. You don't know
who he is and you're like, "What is that
guy doing?" I'm like, "Watch this."
JEFFREY!
IT IS TIME for my nap. Yes, sir, Mr.
Williams.
So, I can't get on the damn bed.
Spent thousands of dollars on something
I can't even use it. It's like getting a
hooker who says, "I only hold hands."
So, my wife and I talk and we come up
with a solution.
I don't know if any of you
own a small dog.
All right. Some of you know where I'm
going with this.
Some of you are very confused right now.
What does a dog have to do with it?
Well,
we have a lot of small dogs in our
country who cannot jump up on couches
and cannot jump up on beds. So, what did
we do? We engineered and built doggie
stairs for our little dogs. There's
doggie stairs for little dogs can run up
and get up on a couch and on a bed. And
I'm here to tell you those little doggie
stairs are [\h__\h] sturdy.
Cuz that's what I do. That's how I get
into my bed every night. I run up doggie
stairs. Yes, I do. People are like,
"Isn't that humiliating?" Absolutely
not. It's fun as hell. I get a good
workout. I'm running up doggie stairs.
Every night I run up those stairs, it's
like I'm passing level one of Super
Mario Brothers.
>> [applause]
>> Sometimes my wife and I role play. She
throws a mushroom at me and yells,
"Grow!"
Having the doggie stairs, not
humiliating.
Buying the doggie stairs,
slightly humiliating.
Cuz I couldn't just order it online. I
had to measure everything in person to
make sure it was all going to fit with
the bed. So, I had to go to a pet store,
a real pet store. I had to find a human
being and walk up to him and be like,
"Hey,
do you have those little stairs
>> [laughter]
>> for dogs?"
The guy's like, "Yeah, sure, no problem.
What breed of dog do you have?" I'm
like, "You son of a bitch."
He's a miniature.
He's like, "All right, well, how heavy's
the dog?" I'm like, "Ah, 120, maybe 130
after the holidays. Don't [\h__\h] judge
me."
"Well, how old IS THE DOG?" "41. GIVE ME
THE [\h__\h] STAIRS."
YES, I'M 41. THIS IS 41, OKAY? I feel
like I have to tell you that this is
what a dwarf looks like at age 41, cuz
you don't have a lot of references.
You're not quite sure how dwarfs age.
The only references you have are
Dinklage and garden gnomes. All right?
This is 41. This is pretty good 41.
Pretty good 41 for a dwarf. Pretty good.
Pretty good.
>> [applause]
>> Yeah.
And it's hard. It's hard to age as a
dwarf, cuz black don't crack, but little
is brittle.
So, here's the last part about the doggy
stairs, okay?
Doggy stairs aren't like beds that have
all these different models and options
and accessories. No, they're doggy
stairs. When I got to the pet shop,
there was one type of doggy stair that
fit the bed that they had in stock,
that's the kind I had to buy. No
choices. So, I brought this thing home,
it fit, it's great. But, this particular
model, it's the doggy stairs, and then
the very top of the stairs,
there's a water bowl.
See, I know some of you guys are like,
"Oh, that's horrible." No, it's not. No,
it's not. Don't feel bad for me, not for
1 second. I got a great life. Oh my god,
I got a beautiful family. I got a
king-size bed in my bedroom. I got doggy
stairs running up to my king-size bed.
And now, I have a hot tub right next to
my KING-SIZE BED.
HELL, YEAH.
OH, WHEN I want bubbles, my wife just
grabs the coffee frother and just
So, you guys got a little bit of insight
into how my brain works. That's how I
solve problems. If I encounter a
problem, I don't cry about it, I don't
get sad about it, I don't go online on
social media, try to humiliate the
manufacturer. I can't believe you don't
make a bed that's dwarf accessible. I
can't believe you're making me spelunk
off my own bed. I can't
I can't believe I have to fire a
grappling hook gun like Batman just to
get my shuteye. I can't believe you did
this [\h__\h] No, I don't do that. If I
have a problem, I shut the hell up, I
get to work, I figure it out, and then I
move the [\h__\h] on with my day. Okay?
That's how I try to do it.
>> [applause]
>> Cuz that's what I was taught.
I was taught by two amazing,
average-sized parents. My parents were
tall, and they taught me that the world
was not built with me in mind. It was
not designed for me, and it was not the
world's job to adjust to my every whim.
It is my job to adjust to the world, to
adjust, to figure it the [\h__\h] out, and
make my own way. Now, is that the proper
way of parenting, the proper lesson?
Who's to say? But, I will tell you that
that's the mindset of almost every
disabled person I know. Disabled people
don't want special attention. Many times
they don't want your help. They want to
be left alone. They want to do it
themselves. They don't want to bother
you. That's why it drives me insane when
I see people fake a disability to get
some kind of benefit. And I see it all
the time, cuz I'm in airports all the
time. People love to fake a disability
in airports, cuz if you're disabled at
the airport, you can board the plane
before anybody else. And the airlines
are not even allowed to ask you what
your disability is, which I think is a
crock of [\h__\h] cuz they ask everything
else about you. How How much liquid do
you have? How big's your nail file? How
big's your bag? They measure your bag in
the bag sizer, right before you get on
the plane. If it's too big, can't carry
it on, check it underneath. I just want
consistency. Measure everything. Measure
the level of disability somebody has if
they want to get on the plane first.
Here's how you do it. Right next to that
bag sizer, you just put a really
disabled [\h__\h]
Okay?
Like a really disabled [\h__\h] And if
you want to board the plane first,
you've got to be more hurt than the hurt
guy, okay? That's the rule.
Some of you were laughing cuz some OF
YOU WERE LIKE, "THAT'S [\h__\h] UP, BRAD."
NO, IT'S NOT. WHAT'S [\h__\h] UP ABOUT IT?
I JUST GAVE HURT a job. That's what I
did. I GAVE HIM A JOB.
>> [applause]
>> BUT YOU'RE being mean to those people.
What people? What people am I being mean
to? Be specific because I never said
what hurt was. I never said what that
was. So, whatever person you just
pictured in your head when I made that
noise, that's on you.
And here's the thing. Anyone who was
offended at that joke, I know you don't
have a disability cuz disabled people
and their families and their friends
have wonderful senses of humor. Amazing
senses of humor.
Dark.
Twisted.
[\h__\h] up senses of humor.
Oh, yeah, they do.
>> [applause]
>> They really do. And even within the
world of disability, there's one
particular disability that has the most
[\h__\h] up sense of humor. Don't worry,
I'll tell you who they are.
Deaf people.
Don't you dare pull back on me now.
Don't you [\h__\h] dare.
I know a lot of you guys are like, "Oh
my god, you're not going to make fun of
deaf people, are you?" Yes, I am.
And if you don't tell them, they'll
never hear about it.
>> [applause]
>> But Brad, they could read your lips.
Fine, let's [\h__\h] with deaf people.
>> Okay, there you go.
Now, I did not know that deaf people
have this amazing sense of humor until
one night I did a show in a theater like
this one, and there were some deaf
people in the audience. And to help them
out, theater was very cool. They
provided a sign language interpreter to
help sign my jokes. I thought that's
very cool, very inclusive, more people
get to enjoy comedy. I'm all for that.
And that was a great show. I told some
jokes, she signed, everybody laughed,
deaf guy laughed like 7 seconds later.
Oh yeah, the whole night, JUST JOKE JOKE
JOKE, HAHAHA.
>> [laughter]
>> Um
>> We're all going to hell, I'm just
driving the bus.
All right.
>> [applause]
>> And if I'm driving, you know it's a
short bus.
So I'm watching her do my act in another
language, which is fascinating. And the
first time I said the word dwarf, I
peeked over cuz I was curious, what's
the sign for dwarf? This is what she
does.
RIGHT IN FRONT OF MY [\h__\h] FACE.
NO HESITATION, NO I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THIS ONE, JUST STRAIGHT UP [\h__\h] YOU,
JUST THAT.
THAT'S DWARF? OH MY WHAT THE HELL IS THE
SIGN FOR BLIND GUY? SON OF A [\h__\h]
AND I LOOK AT HER AND I GO I I TALKED TO
HER, I GO THAT'S THE THAT'S A [\h__\h] UP
SIGN FOR DWARF. She stopped signing,
looks at me and goes yeah.
Kind of has to be.
I'm like what are you talking about?
She's like okay, sign language, it's a
language, right? But we can't use
certain tools that you use with an audio
language, things like voice inflection,
tone, sarcasm, way more difficult when
you're only using your hands to
communicate. And no matter how fast my
hands move, they'll never move as fast
as your mouth does. So, the signs have
to be really obvious so they can be
quickly interpreted and they move on to
the next sign. And when the signs are
obvious, sometimes that comes across as
insensitive or [\h__\h] up.
Oh.
No, that makes a lot of sense. The sign
has to be the most obvious sign for
whatever the word is. She goes,
"Correct." And I go, "Great. What's the
sign for blowjob?"
I'm going to tell you guys right now,
it's exactly what you're thinking.
And now, you can tell how good someone
is at that activity based solely on how
they sign it to you. Yes. Try it out.
Say, "Hey, what's the sign for blowjob?"
That person just goes,
Mwah. They're horrible at that [\h__\h]
They're awful.
But if you say, "What's the sign for
blowjob?" And they just hawk to a spit
on that thing, IT'S LIKE,
THAT'S A happy marriage right there.
So, at that point, I know dwarf, I know
[\h__\h] I don't even care about my
jokes anymore. I just want to learn some
more words.
So, I look at the interpreter and I say,
"What's the sign for gay?"
This is what she does.
Some of you got it. G A Y. Spelled it.
No.
No. [\h__\h] no. You can't do that, deaf
people. You can't do that. You can't BE
LIKE, "DWARF. YEAH. [\h__\h] YEAH.
GAY."
NO.
AND SOME OF YOU ARE LIKE, "WOW, BRAD,
YOU'RE GETTING KIND OF WORKED up about
this." Yeah, I am. I'm mad about this.
I'm mad about this because all the LGBTQ
community has ever asked for
is equality.
They want equality and they deserve
equality. God knows they've earned it.
But here's the thing about equality that
a lot of people forget. Equality doesn't
mean you get to pick and choose just the
good [\h__\h] that you want to incorporate
into your life. No. True equality is you
get all the good [\h__\h] but you get all
the bad [\h__\h] too. That's equality. So,
gay people want to get married. Awesome.
I'm so glad they can. You want to raise
a child with your partner? You should be
able to do that wherever you go on God's
green earth. But only if we get to come
up with a [\h__\h] up sign for you, too.
Oh, yeah. None of this
[\h__\h] No. Next time I say the word
gay, this is what I should see. Just
>> [laughter]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> It's raining men. Hallelujah.
>> [applause]
>> Isn't sign language fun?
Oh my god, I want to learn it. I do. I'm
trying to. And the thing about sign
language, I didn't even realize. It
sounds so obvious now, but at the time I
didn't know. Sign language, just like
any audio language, evolves, changes,
new words are invented and popularized
every year. But with sign language, the
whole community has to agree on the sign
for the word. If there's different signs
for the same word, it might get lost in
translation. I did not realize that
until later. In that very same show, I
did a political joke and I said Trump
and I looked over cuz I was like, she's
probably going to spell Trump. She did
not spell Trump. There's a sign for
Trump. And when she did it, I'm like,
there's no way that's the [\h__\h] sign.
And I went home after the show and I
looked it up. It is the sign. I promise
you guys, according to American Sign
Language, ASL, this is the actual sign
for Donald Trump.
>> [applause]
>> Mwah.
Bravo, deaf people.
Well done. That's the perfect sign. It's
perfect cuz this is not a political
joke. I don't care how you vote. However
you vote, if you see that, you know
exactly who the [\h__\h] we're talking
about, all right?
And let's face it, with Trump, you had
options for other signs. You could have
done other stuff. You could have done
the whole accordion arms he does when he
talks, when he's up there like, "We're
going to have some tariffs." Okay, you
could have done that. Could have done a
little grab 'em by the
You could have done that.
No, perfect sign.
And now,
Trump's out there. He's giving a lot of
speeches, and I'm watching him. I'm
watching all the Trump speeches I can,
cuz every time Trump gives a speech, I
hope and I pray he has a sign language
interpreter with him.
Cuz that man talks in the third person
all the time. Do you have any idea how
[\h__\h] funny this is going to be when
it happens? It's going to happen. He's
going to be up there giving a speech.
"Let me tell you what Donald Trump is
going to do for the United States of
America. Donald Trump is here. Trump
will make America
What the [\h__\h] is that, [\h__\h] What the
[\h__\h] is that?
>> [applause]
>> The poor interpreter, they're just doing
their job. They're going to be like,
That's you, Mr. President. That's you.
That's fake news.
Now,
some might consider that joke political
joke. I'm going to tell you I didn't
intend for it to be a political joke. I
don't want to be a political comedian. I
don't think I'm smart enough to be a
political comedian. Some of them are and
that's great. I'm glad comics are out
there to talk about everything. I'm just
not that guy. I'm not a political comic.
I don't want to say one thing about my
political beliefs and then people think
they know everything about me cuz no,
that's not how it is. I'm a very
complicated person as are a lot of you.
We have a lot of mixed opinions about
everything. If you are one of these
people, no matter which side you
support, that is so into your side that
you find them infallible. They think
they can do nothing wrong. Whatever they
say, you will do. You will not question.
You go where they want. You believe what
they want. You are mad at the things
they want you to be mad at. If that is
you, call your mom. You're in a [\h__\h]
cult.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> And
surround yourself with people that think
differently than you. Challenge
yourself. Don't stay in these bubbles.
This is a college basketball town, okay?
Yeah. Yeah, big college basketball town.
One of the greatest college basketball
coaches of all time was a guy named John
Wooden. John Wooden had a bunch of
quotes, but one of my favorites is he
used to say, "When everyone thinks
alike, nobody thinks."
I want you to think. I want you to have
people around you that have different
opinions than you. You can talk it out.
Be civil about it. Maybe you arrive at a
compromise. Surround yourself with
different types of people. My friends,
they look different than me, clearly.
I'm not friends with all dwarves. I'm
not just walking into a Starbucks going,
"Hello, I'm a dwarf." Okay, like like
like that's not happening.
My wife is different than me. I love her
very much. Her friends, different than
me. They're all great except Carol. [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h] I hate her.
I hate Carol. That's a real thing, okay?
That's a Okay, for those of you who
don't know, Carol is a real person.
She's actually my wife's friend and I do
not change her name for the stage, okay?
I know I
I want this, okay? I want all the
[\h__\h] smoke. Bring it. All right. Now,
in my last special called Starfish, I
did about 5 minutes all on Carol, all
right?
Here's an update.
She saw it.
Yeah? And now she is threatening a
lawsuit against me. Mhm. She wants to
sue me for defamation of character, all
right? And when she told me that, I told
her bring it the [\h__\h] on, Carol, okay?
Bring it the [\h__\h] on. I want you to see
Okay, okay, we got this camera right
here? Okay. She might be watching this,
okay? So, Carol, look right at me. I
want you to [\h__\h] sue me, okay?
Please, for the love of God, sue me. If
you sue me, you're going to have to
prove in a court of law you're not a
[\h__\h]
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> Now,
that's a very strong word.
I don't like to use that word. I don't.
So, I learned the sign for it.
>> [cheering]
>> The sign was taught to me by a friend
and a brilliant comedian. His name is
Jim Jefferies, and this is the sign for
it, okay? You do You do like a
a diamond like that, but then you just
do it aggressively, okay? So, like,
that's just vagina, but then you want to
do the C-word, it's like
like that.
And also, just so you know, that works
for all kind of derogatory stronger
language for the C-word, all of them.
So, you can have a lot of fun with it.
Like, you can make a W with these three
fingers, and then you could just like
flip the W over on your hand like that,
and then you you do the sign [\h__\h]
waffle.
All right.
Bust that one out at Thanksgiving in
front of the in-laws. Have some fun.
>> [laughter]
>> Now, a lot of people ask me, Brad, why
do you hate this Carol woman so much?"
Who?
>> [laughter]
>> Allow me to explain.
When my wife and I found out that we
were going to become parents, we were
stoked. We were thrilled. We were very
thankful. We were excited. We told
everyone. Everyone was very excited for
us. When we found out that our daughter
has dwarfism, we were excited. We told
everyone. They were very excited for us.
And then we told Carol.
And I'll never forget this. It was in
our home. She was visiting and I broke
the news. I was like, "Carol, Carol,
Carol,
you want to know why she's not drinking?
She's pregnant. We're having a kid. Oh
my god, we're going to be we're going to
be parents and we're going to have a
perfect little girl and she's got
dwarfism so she's going to be a little
person just like me." And Carol looked
at me and goes,
"Oh, Brad,
female and a dwarf, her life is going to
be too hard."
Now, you guys have known me now for a
little more than an hour.
I think you guys know my vibe. My vibe
is you can say stuff to me. That's okay.
Say stuff to me, I'll say stuff to you.
Hopefully, we'll be friends afterward.
Nothing wrong with that.
Until Carol said that [\h__\h] all right?
That was different.
When you said my daughter's life is
going to be too hard because of her
dwarfism, I realized that what you were
saying in that sentence was
any hardship, any struggle, any
complications my daughter has in her
life that are because of dwarfism,
those are my fault.
And the worst part, Lexington,
I believed her.
And I got really depressed and it was
bad. I was not fun to be around for a
while. Thankfully, I have amazing
family. I have wonderful friends. They
encouraged me to get professional help
and I did. I started going to therapy. I
still go to therapy. I go to therapy
every week. And I'm going to tell you
guys right now, it's one of the best
decisions I've ever made in my entire
life.
>> [applause]
>> And I say that not to get that applause,
although thank you for it. I say that
because I need someone to hear that who
needs to hear that right now, whether it
be in this theater or watching at home.
There's someone going through some [\h__\h]
and they're wondering how to deal with
it. And those coping mechanisms and
those tools can be found in therapy.
That's all therapy is. It's a tool to
help you get through life. That's all it
is. Like a hammer.
>> [applause]
>> Hammer is a tool to help you hammer a
nail. Therapy is a screwdriver that
keeps a screw from coming loose, okay?
And as much as I was singing the praises
of of of professional help, the best
help came from my wife. And I'll never
forget this. I was having a particularly
bad day. My wife noticed. And she looks
at me and she goes, "Okay, Brad. I get
it. I get why you're upset. You're upset
because you believe you are passing on
trauma to our child. And I'm here to
tell you this.
There's been thousands of dwarfs that
have come before her. There will be
millions of dwarfs that come after her.
There will always be a little person in
this world whether we decide to have a
child or not. And out of all those
little people whoever have, never will
exist, I truly believe our daughter is
the luckiest one of all of them. Our
daughter is the luckiest one because she
gets to be guided by Brad [\h__\h]
Williams as her father.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> That brought me out. That did. Because
in that moment I realized, "Holy [\h__\h]
she's right. Yes, dwarfism has its
struggles, has its complications, but
life has struggles. Life has
complications. Everyone in this room has
gone through some [\h__\h] at some point in
your life. But how much better would it
have been if the person who loved you
more than anything in this world went
through the exact same thing, had the
answers, and could help guide you along
the way? Cuz that's what I could do for
my kid. I've lived this life. I've
thrived in this life. I have the cheat
codes to win at this life.
So,
when my daughter comes to me and goes,
"Daddy, I have a problem." I'm like,
"Don't worry, I got this. Up, up, down,
down, left, right, left, right, A, B, A,
B, select, start. Okay, I'm good to go."
>> [applause]
>> Because being a parent is hard. It's
difficult. A lot of parents wonder
things like, "Will my child be bullied
in school?" I know my kid's going to be
bullied in school. You don't think I'm
not preparing for that [\h__\h] You don't
think as a stand-up comedian I'm not
writing the most vicious
roast joke-style comebacks possible? I
pity the little [\h__\h] that makes fun
of my kid at school. All right? Not
going to go well for them because I know
the bully mentality. A bully will look
at my daughter and think, "That's a weak
little girl." But she's not going to be.
She's going to be a one-woman verbal
assault unit.
>> [cheering]
>> Oh, yeah.
>> [applause]
>> Some kid's going to come up, "Look at
how little you are." She'll be like,
"Yeah? Look how you color. Who taught
you? Michael J. Fox?"
"Well, you're a midget." You're right,
but I'm only here cuz my parents love
each other. You're here cuz your mom
doesn't swallow.
Okay.
I'm not worried about my kid.
My kid's going to be just fine because
my daughter is the best possible
combination of my wife and I put
together. My daughter is the combination
of a brilliant, beautiful, driven,
independent Chinese woman and an
acid-tongued
dwarf.
That's a hell of a combination.
Do you want to know what that
combination makes when Chinese and dwarf
come together? It makes an emoji.
>> [laughter]
>> No, I'm the proud father of an Asian
dwarf. I really am. And I realized as a
father of an Asian dwarf,
I'm in a win-win situation. I am. Cuz if
I'm the best father in the world to an
Asian dwarf,
she changes the world. She inspires
others. She shatters a glass ceiling.
She leads by example. The world becomes
a better place just because she existed
in it.
And if I am the worst father in the
world to an Asian dwarf,
we get the most revolutionary porn star
of all time.
I know, that's a difficult one to laugh
at, isn't it? That's a hard one.
That's a hard one. Some of you are very
confused right now. Some of you are
laughing. Some of you are like,
"Absolutely not." A couple of you sick
[\h__\h] are like, "Come on, SEVEN." HEY.
HEY.
I KNOW that's a weird joke. I WROTE THAT
JOKE, OKAY? I remember. I remember
writing it and staring at my notepad
going, "Oh, I don't know about that
one."
But then,
I found something out. Not sure if you
guys are aware of a website called
OnlyFans.
>> [laughter]
>> For those of you who don't know,
OnlyFans is a website where anyone can
go on the website and release content.
Any kind of content you want. And if
people like your content, they can pay
you for it. They can subscribe to your
page. You can earn some money from it.
Now, the content can be anything.
But the vast majority of the people on
this website are putting out
adult-themed material. There's hundreds
of thousands of people on this website
who are trying to make money.
But do you know what woman made the most
money on this website last year?
Female dwarf.
Do you know how much money this woman
made?
$63 million.
Did you hear what the [\h__\h] I just said?
I read a female dwarf made $63 million
in one year putting out adult themed
material and I WAS LIKE, "WOW!
I CAN MISS SOME RECITALS."
>> [laughter]
>> You guys are so much fun. Oh my
goodness.
Oh, this is a lot of fun and the past
few years have been a lot of fun. My
life has changed dramatically. I've got
more popular. I've moved from wonderful
comedy clubs to beautiful theaters like
this one and it's truly a trip and it's
a blessing and it's weird cuz it has
impacted me in ways I never thought
about. Like now my wife gets recognized
on the street. That's weird. I did not
think about that. It's always women that
recognize her and she tells me about it.
Everyone usually asks the same question.
They all come up and they're like, "Are
you Brad Williams' wife?" And she's
like, "Yeah." And then they just look at
her and go,
"One time I [\h__\h] a little guy, too."
And she'll be like, "Oh, you [\h__\h] a
dwarf?" And they're like, "No, he was
5'5". NOT THE SAME [\h__\h] THING!
NOT THE SAME [\h__\h] THING! NOT EVEN
CLOSE TO THE SAME [\h__\h] THE 5'5 IS NOT
A DWARF. I HAVE A SCIENTIFIC CONDITION.
I HAVE A GENETIC MUTATION called
achondroplastic dwarfism. If you're 5'5,
YOU DON'T HAVE THAT. GOD JUST LOOKED AT
YOU AND WENT, "UGH, I've had enough.
Fuck."
That's all that happened and you don't
KNOW MY LIFE. 5'5, YOU DON'T KNOW MY
LIFE. You don't know my struggle. You
never walked into a shoe store and said,
"Hey, bring me out every shoe that fits
me." The only shoe they bring out has
lights blinking from the [\h__\h] OKAY? YOU
DON'T KNOW.
AND DON'T EVEN THINK FOR ONE second that
sex with a 5'5 guy is the same as
[\h__\h] a dwarf. Way different. 5'5, you
still have average size arms. You have
average size arms. You still get on top.
You do missionary. Then you can push
down. You can push down. And then you go
up. You go up. And then your lady has no
little space to work with right there.
Yeah, you have that space. Ladies here
with me, no space, little arms, I am
right [\h__\h] there. Okay, right there.
I'm right there. I'm in your ear the
entire time. It's not sexy. I don't
sound sexy. I sound like a truffle pig.
Okay?
I'm just in your ear the entire time
like
Almost there.
AND I'M VERY INSECURE ABOUT HOW I SOUND
IN THE BEDROOM. BUT MY WIFE just looks
at me AND GOES, "FUCK ME, PIG BOY!" AND
I'M LIKE,
SETH LEPOND.
LEXINGTON, KENTUCKY, I cannot thank you
enough for being here tonight.
>> [music]
[cheering]
[music]
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yeah.
>> [music]